The Brute’s strength is unmatched: they can hit hard and knock people out. They can take a turn to prepare for a massive blow, or throw their weapon from a distance to unaware foes.
The Medic’s knowledge and skills allow them to heal crew members, as well as inflicting bleeding damage to foes until death. During a fight, the Medic can splash the whole crew with rum to heal everyone at once.
The Cook is essential to any crew as they provide hot meals, strength and support, using the power of tasty food and inspiring words. The crew will fight even harder whenever a feast is announced.
The Cannoneer’s perfect aim is what makes them such a deadly shot. They use clever abilities to protect themselves, or create fiery explosions with their knowledge of the black powder.
The Crook is a sly taunter who can break their enemy's morale. A good insult is a perfect distraction to disrupt foes and even steal their money. When things get too hot, The Crook can make the whole crew escape from the fight in a flash.